

Dillon Smith

Email: dillsmth@gmail.com

Phone: 612-413-5856

Github: https://github.com/dillon-smith-us

1

PROFILE

I'm a recent Graduate from Minneapolis College with an Associates in Design with focus in Architectural Technologies. I'm very well rounded in Microsoft Office, Adobe CC, and AutoCAD. I am currently enrolled at the University of Minnesota Full stack developer bootcamp, and am learning javascript. I consider myself a quick learner, good listener, and also a leader when called upon. I have experience in manufacturing, customer service, and IT environments. I'm easygoing, and love learning new work environments!

2

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

FREELANCE DESIGN - 2020 - Current

Freelance Graphic Designer

My freelance projects have included NFT creations on rarible, superrare, and opensea platforms. These digital art libraries of mine are mostly filled with adobe software animated gifs, and blender software animations.

PROTOLABS - 2017 - Current

Certified C level Technician

Protolabs is a rapid prototyping manufacturing company making parts on demand for many different industries. I am inspector of build, and milling, and a facilitator of quality and functionality on the floor. My position requires a keen eye, analyzing problems in 3D images from our company's custom design software, as well as analyzing problems in physical parts. I was an inspection

trainer for build and milling departments of the production team.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY (CONTINUED)

TEN-K Solar - 2015 - 2017

Warehouse IT assistant

Ten-K solar was a solar energy company specializing in the production of solar panels and solar batteries. I worked closely with their multiple production teams, and aided solving technical problems, as well as set-ups with the IT team.

3

EDUCATION

Minneapolis College 2016 - 2019

Associates Degree - Graphic Design

Graduated in winter of 2019 with Associates degree in Graphic Design. Degree included an immersive education in brand and portfolio development, including AutoCAD, and Adobe software mastery.

University of Minnesota 2021 -

Currently Enrolled - Full Stack Developer Bootcamp

Learning front end and back end web development. Proficient in HTML/CSS. Becoming fluent in javascript, mySQL, and node.is.